You
Where'd everyone go?
You didn't tell them where I was?
I thought they heard you
On the way back from our workplace visit, we got split up from the rest of the group
I'm sorry, I didn't mean it
No worries, the next train will be here soon
It's not like we're in a rush, or lost, or anything
Hey, quit smiling, you idiot!
Quit feeling like you lucked out!
The next one is in seven minutes
Let's take a seat
I'm the only one who feels like they lucked out here
I bet she's super embarrassed getting stuck here with just me
That's probably why she's crying
Go on, nothing to see here
It must look like I made her cry
I guess, maybe I did
Um, here, it's fine, have a drink
That won't do it, huh?
You know, it was my fault for going to the bathroom then
Sorry, I should've just announced it to everyone or something, I guess
This I pledge! I now will go to the bathroom!
Like some declaration?
Hey!
Why are you over there?
We'll see you next week.
I'm sad because I don't have to cry
I fell on my head
Not yet 보고s
I'm about to go crazy
BROOK
It'd be as much 900
Before you get involved too, Govern Writing
And I thought more about the migration
If you want more, I never think I can
少ない裏切の中
僕らは身も分かぬまま
I have no idea how well-known of a model Yamada is to people, but there might be some here
who recognize her. Given her looks, I wouldn't be surprised.
Musashi Koyama. Musashi Koyama.
Stay or we'll get split up.
Hara's group got to all go to Nagasaki Hut. So lucky.
Yeah, but they might not get to eat there. Personally, I thought this was fun enough myself. Especially now.
Me too. You think those two are gonna go out?
I don't know.
Pretty crazy dating someone from the same class, huh?
Yeah.
I remember kids forming couples back in elementary school. Always holding hands.
Though honestly, I think it might be more fun to keep things a secret.
And you? What do you think?
What do you think?
Uh...
Senzoku.
Y-yeah.
Uh, maybe. Sure.
I can hardly focus on a word she says!
Oh!
Huh?
Someone spoiled her!
Oh, great.
Gee, sorry.
No, I'm the one who should be sorry!
Huh?
I was so focused on being on time since I was in charge of our group that I didn't even notice.
This was all my fault. I'm really sorry.
It's okay. All of us make mistakes.
You're one to talk!
Seriously. Our workplace visit ended up being a real mess.
They were asking rude questions, running off from each other and getting split up.
Airheads. Every single one of them.
You know, Kyo, you already told us all that yesterday.
What? Yes! Yesterday I was only telling Mom about it!
I better get going.
Seems to me like you've been enjoying school lately.
Huh?
Enjoying school.
Yeah, right.
I still don't have any friends.
Is it because I like Yamata?
Like this gloomy little creepy freak would even read anything as lighthearted as that!
Can't let it get in my head.
I know they're really just making fun of me.
I'm the one who will end up hurt in the end.
Good morning!
Hey!
Morning!
Yamata? Why are you out here?
Um, no reason, just...
She thinks she's a gym teacher or something?
Is she waiting for someone?
Guess that's got nothing to do with me.
Uh!
Huh?
Hm?
Hey there, good morning.
Y-y-yeah.
That was close.
I wouldn't have spotted you if not for the bike.
Uh, right.
So, um...
Here.
Huh?
I said I'd lend them to you.
Mm-hmm.
Oh!
Don't you wanna read them?
She was serious about all that?
N-no, I do.
But why...
Give them now?
Oh, because I'm leaving school early today.
Oh.
It's a really super good manga!
The main character's so great, their friend dies at one point and a whole lot happens.
But that cool-looking guy on the back cover turns out to be a really sweet guy and...
Is it me or did you just spoil something huge?
N-no!
That's only, like, volume three, closer to the beginning of it, so...
I've heard enough!
N-no!
Make sure you read it, okay?
Weren't you... busy?
With what?
Weren't you... waiting for someone there at the front gate?
Huh?
Yeah.
I was waiting.
See ya.
Hmm?
Hmm...
Yamada sometimes leaves early or stays home from school for work reasons.
Oh!
You're sitting down today!
I...
Thought you left early!
Thought I'd swing by.
Wait a minute, Ichikawa.
Last time I told you to sit, you said...
N-no!
It's easier to remember stuff you read standing up!
You did say that, right?
Oh!
Give me a break!
Hey!
That's not Kimi-oct!
Ugh!
I prefer to read manga at home privately.
Read it now!
D-
This is a really grotesque book!
Stop!
D-
Sorry!
D- No, I'm sorry.
D-
No, I am.
Maybe I do enjoy school.
Kimi-iro Octave.
I wonder how she usually reads.
Like this?
Or this?
Like that!
Did you read it?
N-no. Not yet.
I couldn't concentrate on it yesterday.
If you don't hurry, I'm gonna spoil it all.
You spoiled enough already!
Uhhh...
Can't just go reading it in class, either.
Ichikawa?
What the hell?
What are you doing just talking to Yamada like that?
Shoot!
What? Aren't we classmates, though?
Don't you two seem a little close?
No, we...
Finally turned to bullying, has he?
Hey, man.
Think Yamada's got a crush on anyone?
I mean, forget a crush.
I'll bet she's got a boyfriend.
You know what I mean?
But not like I care or anything.
Just a bit curious is all.
Is he trying to open up?
I figured if you two were especially close,
maybe you'd know if she had a boyfriend or not, do ya?
Uh, not really.
I do know she doesn't have one.
Oh, well then.
Don't tell anyone I asked.
You understand, right?
Uh, right.
Yeah.
It's pretty crazy going for Yamada, though.
True.
But...
Can't help who we like.
Know what I mean?
Yeah, I do.
Talk about embarrassing, though.
So, when did it start?
I guess I only noticed recently.
When, exactly?
I mean, if you really wanna know, well...
This is pretty embarrassing to put out there.
Heh.
By stopping able to wink to her.
I never should've asked.
You know, they say you can't wink to the girls you really like.
And, turns out it's true!
Huh?
What?
Nothing?
So, like, that's weird feeling...
Is that true?
You know?
Does that mean...
I don't really like her then?
What are you gonna do?
Is she just some sexual fantasy?
Yo!
You even listening?
Wha...
What do you like about her?
What?
Are you blind or something, man?
So, her face then?
What else is there?
There's plenty!
She's got a nice banging figure, too.
That's still just how she looks.
She's got a nice rack, but those legs...
Thin and long, but still nice and plump in that hot sorta way.
Like two juicy sticks.
I'm heading back.
Huh?
Hey, listen, Ichikawa!
You better not tell anyone, you hear?
Man, why do I feel so gross?
It wasn't that long ago.
It only used to irk me a little when they'd talk dirty about her.
I've eyed her up plenty myself.
So, why does it bother me now?
Wow!
That's totes crazy!
How did you know what she was saying?
Just guessing with context.
Wow.
I mean, I'm just guessing.
Is this feeling a sign?
I really like her?
I just kinda have a hunch.
That's Ayashiko for you!
Okay, quiz time.
Tell me what am I saying, okay?
Ho-he-fu-ho-ro-ho-he-fu!
Huh?
Wait, what?
Come again?
What was that?
Ho-he-fu-ho-ro-he-fu!
Right on the money.
What does that even mean?
That's it.
I guess.
Right?
Don't write me!
I guess...
I really am looking at her in that sorta way.
Does that mean I don't actually like her?
What will I do?
Uh...
I can't snack anymore.
Talk about getting serious over snacks!
This sign wasn't up on this board before, was it?
Now that you've mentioned it, it wasn't.
But it's already obvious that you can't eat in the library.
That's what I'm talking about!
If it's so obvious to everyone, why bother to even post this now?
I mean, no one ever eats here in the library.
Hang on a minute!
Was that a Yamada joke?
I'm just saying.
Someone must know I eat in here.
It's suspicious that this note is on the board now.
Maybe.
Gotta figure out who ratted you out.
The only people who know about you are Kobayashi, Sekine, Yoshida, Hara, Kanzaki, Kanaoya...
Wait, now let's not go down that line of reason.
I'm sure plenty of other people have been in and out of here, too.
Doesn't like to stir up trouble, huh?
Let's go ask the library teacher.
She'll know about the sign.
Mm-hmm.
Come to think of it, they saw that snack bag in the trash before, didn't they?
Maybe that's why?
Impossible!
No way.
That doesn't make any sense to me.
I promise you I never threw anything away in there.
Then...
Maybe...
Someone else is behind all this.
I really doubt that.
Huh?
That one wasn't a joke?!
Oh, that new sign.
Yeah, I just thought...
It was weird, there was a sign for something so obvious!
I found this on the floor.
Ugh.
It might just be one little lozenge, but if we allow this to pass, there's no stopping others.
Sometimes people don't realize the obvious until we write it out for them.
Hey, don't you have something to say?
Say something!
Does this mean...
That today...
Is the last day Yamada will come to the library?
I guess...
She has no reason to be here...
If she can't eat...
Well...
Not like I care.
She only talked to me because I just happened to be here anyway.
Huh?!
I knew all along we couldn't eat here.
As far as I'm concerned, one little sign didn't change anything.
What's with this girl?!
I knew all the risks from the very beginning!
Quit making it sound cool!
If the library teacher catches you with that in your mouth, you'll...
Even still...
I...
Still...
Like her...
So much...
I...
that was that was really close just now
was that too weird for her
sorry i thought she might take them away or even kick you out
huh did it melt you should wash your hands
go away
huh
you know
you should lay off the snacks seriously
this is how it should be over with
all of it
i i thought i'd do my homework
yeah
i'm laying off the snacks like you said i should a whole third
the problem wasn't the amount
yamada never changes
oh
EXPECTATION
素直になれないいつまでもこのままでいたいかも
そんな気持ちは解けた
僕らは探してたお揃いの心を
僕らは交わしてたまとまらない台詞を
触れたい手の熱がここまで届いて 僕は背伸びしてた 大人見てる 君は見て したいんだ 君のこと
力消えたって 夢じゃないなんて 心が痛くて もっと 言葉にしたくて
Yamada, think about it. Who else could have thrown something away in here?
Wasn't it you?
Huh?
Remember way back to that one day?
Shh.
That's bad.
No, I never threw that away.
What? Why not?
Well...
It's trash.
You brought it home?
What's that?
Oof!